# Patricia Betancor Jimenez

**Web Developer and Designer** 

Address:

25 Swindon street, GL51 9ES Cheltenham

Phone:

07435 859423

**Email:** 

patriciabetancorjimenez@gmail.com

## **Summary**

Web developer and designer with ability to create responsive websites from development to production stage. Focused on writing clean and reusable code. Experienced in e-commerce and customer relations. Creative professional with high attention to detail and drive to solve problems both within a team and independently.

PORTFOLIO - www.pbjportfolio.com

### **Skills**

- HTML 5
- CSS
- Sass

- Bootstrap 4
- JavaScript ES6
- JQuery

- Git & GitHub
- PHP Mailer
- API

## **Experience**

-Web Developer Experience: 2019-present

Created different projects where the main actions and technologies used were:

- Built fully responsive websites using Media Queries and Bootstrap 4 and tested browser compatibility.
- Added styles with Sass, advanced CSS and BEM methodology.
- Implemented web functionality with JavaScript ES6 and Document Object Model manipulation.
- Validated forms with JQuery or Bootstrap plug-ins.
- Fetched data from an API and displayed it on the website.
- Corrected bugs by using the developer console.
- Used Git main commands for version control.

-International customer service advisor: 2015 - present

E-commerce, Superdry PLC, Cheltenham, United Kingdom

• Collaborated daily with over 75 customers and business partners (Amazon, Zalando and eBay) and reported website errors to the IT department.

## **Education**

-Web development courses: 2019-present

Udemy Acadamy, online courses

-Degree in Chemical Engineering: Graduation in 2015 University in Las Palmas de Gran Canaria, Spain

### **Others**